Preliminary Inventory of the John Dinges papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Aquilino Boyd (Box-folder 30: 3)
- Blandon (Box-folder 30: 4)
- N, N-S (Box-folder 30: 5)
- N, T-Z (Box-folder 30: 6)
- Notes, Spadafora (Box-folder 30: 7)
- Notes, Barletta (Box-folder 30: 8)
- WP/NYT (Box-folder 30: 9)
- N, D-G (Box-folder 30: 10)
- N, H-M (Box-folder 30: 11)
- Our Man reviews (Box-folder 30: 12)
- Appointment book, 1988 (Box-folder 30: 13)
- Panama, updated chapter (Box-folder 30: 14)
- NSA (Box-folder 30: 15)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 30: 16)
- Panama, FOIA (Box-folder 30: 17)
- Marco A. Gandasegui, Centroamerica y el Canal de Panama (Box-folder 30: 18)
- FOIA form letter (Box-folder 30: 19)
- FOIA, addresses & NSA archives (Box-folder 30: 20)
- FOIA form letter (Box-folder 30: 21)
- Letters (Box-folder 30: 22)
- Random House (Box-folder 30: 23)
- Fund for Investigative Journalism (Box-folder 30: 24)
- Outline (Box-folder 30: 25)
- Panama (Box-folder 31: 1)
- Notes, Jan.-Feb. 1988 (Box-folder 31: 2)
- Kerry hearings (Box-folder 31: 3)
- Docs, Kerry hearings (Box-folder 31: 4)
- Kerry Committee, Awan docs, Part 2 (Box-folder 31: 5)
- Notes, Mar.-May 1988 (Box-folder 31: 6)
- Carlton Turner (Box-folder 31: 7)
- Unlabeled folder (Box-folder 31: 8)
- N, Strickler (Box-folder 31: 9)
- N, Sayre (Box-folder 31: 10)
- Villalaz (Box-folder 31: 11)
- N, Stone (Box-folder 31: 12)
- N, Miranda (Box-folder 31: 13)
- N, Noriega (Box-folder 31: 14)
- N, Jordan (Box-folder 31: 15)
- Notes, Boris Martinez (Box-folder 31: 16)
- Notes, G. Lewis (Box-folder 31: 17)
- Kalish, Steve (Box-folder 31: 18)
- Gorostiaga (Box-folder 31: 19)
- N, DH book (Box-folder 31: 20)
- N, DH tape transcript (Box-folder 31: 21)
- Kerry Committee, Daniel G. Murphy (Box-folder 32: 1)
- Kerry Committee, Sarkis Soghenalian (Box-folder 32: 2)
- Kerry Committee, John McCann (Box-folder 32: 3)
- BCCI, Awan (Box-folder 32: 4)
- Kerry, Blandon (Box-folder 32: 5)
- Kerry, Betzner (Box-folder 32: 6)
- Kerry Committee, Franklin J. Camper (Box-folder 32: 7)
- Kerry Committee, Richard D. Gregorie (Box-folder 32: 8)
- Kerry, Milian R. (Box-folder 32: 9)
- Kerry Committee, Awan docs, Part 1 (Box-folder 32: 10)
- Congress, Bayh report (Box-folder 33: 1)
- Kerry, Vogel (Box-folder 33: 2)
- Helms role (Box-folder 33: 3)
- Drugs, Oscar Esquella (Box-folder 33: 4)
- Jimmy Carter & treaties (Box-folder 33: 5)
- Assassination plots (Box-folder 33: 6)
- Drugs, Torrijos (Box-folder 33: 7)
- Kerry Committee, Felix Rodriguez (Box-folder 33: 8)
- Kerry Committee, Nestor D. Sanchez (Box-folder 33: 9)
- Kerry, Ramon Milian (Box-folder 33: 10)
- Kerry, George Morales (Box-folder 33: 11)
- Kerry hearings, Frank McNeil (Box-folder 33: 12)
- Kerry, Palmer (Box-folder 33: 13)
- Kerry Committee, Jack C. Lawn (Box-folder 33: 14)
- Computer disks (Box-folder 34: 1)
- Congressional hearings (Box-folder 34: 2)
- Banking, Panama (Box-folder 34: 3)
- Panama, Economy, 1989 (Box-folder 34: 4)
- Panama, Spadafora, 1990 (Box-folder 34: 5)
- Mass grave (Box-folder 34: 6)
- Panama, aid (Box-folder 34: 7)
- Panama, Albrook (Box-folder 34: 8)
- Panama, stories, clips, ideas (Box-folder 34: 9)
- BCCI (Box-folder 34: 10)
- Panama, Spadafora lawsuit (Box-folder 34: 11)
- Speech, Women's National Democratic Club (Box-folder 34: 12)
- Nancy Palmer Agency (Box-folder 34: 13)
- Panama, Colon (Box-folder 34: 14)
- Drugs, Cheryl papers (Box-folder 34: 15)
- Drugs, Torrijos (Box-folder 34: 16)
- Drugs, Watson deposition (Box-folder 34: 17)
- Drugs, Cheryl (Box-folder 34: 18)
- May 4, 1988, House Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 35: 1)
- June 1, 1988, House Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 35: 2)
- July 28, 1988, House Judiciary (Box-folder 35: 3)
- Sept. 28, 1988, House Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 35: 4)
- Oct. 6, 1988, Gejdenson (Box-folder 35: 5)
- Jan. 12, 1989, Senate Foreign Relations (Box-folder 35: 6)
- Mar. 29, 1988, House Narcotics (Box-folder 35: 7)
- House Appropriations (Box-folder 35: 8)
- House Foreign Operations (Box-folder 35: 9)
- Mar. 10, 1988, House Appropriations (Box-folder 35: 10)
- Mar. 10, 1988, House Merchant Marine (Box-folder 35: 11)
- Mar. 29, 1988, House Select (Box-folder 35: 12)
- Mar. 9, 1988, House Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 35: 13)
- Mar. 10, 1988, House Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 35: 14)
- Oct. 22, 1987, Senate Western Hemisphere (Box-folder 35: 15)
- Mar. 3, 1988, House Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 35: 16)
- Mar. 20, 1980, House Armed Services (Box-folder 35: 17)
- Feb. 21-23, 1984, House Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 35: 18)
- Aug. 1, 1984, House Western Hemisphere (Box-folder 35: 19)
- Apr. 29-July 23, 1986, House Western Hemisphere (Box-folder 35: 20)
- June 29, 1986, House Select (Box-folder 35: 21)
- June 18-25, 1987, House Foreign Affairs (Box-folder 35: 22)
- Sept. 1987, Senate Caucus on International Narcotics Control (Box-folder 35: 23)
- Aug. 28, 1985, Senate Governmental Affairs (Box-folder 35: 24)
- June 6-July 10, 1979, House Merchant Marine (Box-folder 35: 25)
- Panama, Nexis (Box-folder 36: 1)
- Trial, Nov. 1991 (Box-folder 36: 2)
- FOIA, docs (Box-folder 36: 3)
- CNN tapes (Box-folder 36: 4)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 36: 5)
- General clips, 1991-92 (Box-folder 36: 6)
- Panama article, Nov. 1991 (Box-folder 36: 7)
- Clips, Apr.-May 1991 (Box-folder 36: 8)
- Congressional hearings (Box-folder 36: 9)
- Panama psyops (Box-folder 37: 1)
- The NNICC Report, 1987 (Box-folder 37: 2)
- Drug Control: U.S. International Narcotics Control Activities (Box-folder 37: 3)
- Drug Control: U.S.-Supported Efforts in Colombia and Bolivia (Box-folder 37: 4)
- Panama: 16 anos de lucha contra el narcotrafico (Box-folder 37: 5)
- Panama: 16 anos de lucha contra el narcotrafico, vol. 2 (Box-folder 37: 6)
- Panama: 16 Years of Struggle against Drug Traffic (Box-folder 37: 7)
- Miscellaneous press releases and printed matter (Box-folder 37: 8)
- General Manuel Antonio Noriega (National Security Archive) (Box-folder 37: 9)
- FBIS, Panama (Box-folder 37: 10)
- Verdict, 1992 (Box-folder 37: 11)
- Congressional hearings (Box-folder 38: 1)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 38: 2)
- Panama, 1992 (Box-folder 38: 3)
- Ramon Milian (Box-folder 38: 4)
- National Security Archive (Box-folder 38: 5)
- U.S. v. Noriega trial transcripts (Box-folder 38: 6)
- Verdugo, Gonzales (Box-folder 38: 7)
- Miscellany (Box-folder 38: 8)
- Frontline: War and Peace in Panama (video) (Box-folder 39: 1)
- Frontline: Guns, Drugs and the CIA (video) (Box-folder 39: 2)
- The Panama Invasion Revisited (video) (Box-folder 39: 3)
- Steven Kalish (tape) (Box-folder 39: 4)
- Senate Foreign Relations hearings/Lobe (tape) (Box-folder 39: 5)
- Kalish (tape) (Box-folder 39: 6)
- Kalish/Rosenblat (tape) (Box-folder 39: 7)
- Hearings/Rodriguez (tape) (Box-folder 39: 8)
- Sayre (tape) (Box-folder 39: 9)
- Foreign Relations hearings (tape) (Box-folder 39: 10)
- Senate staff (tape) (Box-folder 39: 11)
- unlabeled tape (Box-folder 39: 12)
- unlabeled tape (Box-folder 39: 13)
- unlabeled tape (Box-folder 39: 14)
- Senate hearings/Gorman (tape) (Box-folder 39: 15)
- unlabeled tape (Box-folder 39: 16)
- Raul Leis, Comando sur poder hostil (Box-folder 40: 1)
- Panama: A Country Study (Box-folder 40: 2)
- Congressional hearings (Box-folder 40: 3)
- Ricardo Arias Calderon, Panama: Desastre o democracia! (Box-folder 41: 1)
- Miscellaneous printed matter (Box-folder 41: 2)
- Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Feb. 9-10, 1988 (Box-folder 41: 3)
- Notes, Dec. 1988 (Box-folder 41: 4)
- The Brenneke Report (Box-folder 41: 5)
- Kalish transcript (Box-folder 41: 6)
- Outline (Box-folder 41: 7)
- North & Noriega (Box-folder 41: 8)
- Cadi Simon (Box-folder 41: 9)
- Chile, movie idea (Box-folder 41: 10)
- Gulf War & media (Box-folder 41: 11)
- LA projects, contracts (Box-folder 41: 12)
- Maps (Box-folder 41: 13)
- Gitenstein, Bushong (Box-folder 41: 14)
- Authors Guild Bulletin issues (Box-folder 42: 1)
- Panama: A Second Look (Box-folder 42: 2)
- Panama: Hacia un modelo policial (Box-folder 42: 3)
- Panama (Box-folder 42: 4)
- Panama, names (Box-folder 42: 5)
- Panama, Noriega chronology (Box-folder 42: 6)
- Panama, 1990 death toll (Box-folder 42: 7)
- Noriega questions (Box-folder 42: 8)
- Kozak testimony (Box-folder 42: 9)
- Noriega, conduct during invasion (Box-folder 42: 10)
- Reinaldo Ruiz, drugs (Box-folder 42: 11)
- Banking dispute (Box-folder 42: 12)
- G. Endara, drug link (Box-folder 42: 13)
- Clips, Panama, Dec. 1989 (Box-folder 42: 14)
- Panama, Jan. 1990 (Box-folder 42: 15)
- Panama clips, Feb.-Sept. 1990 (Box-folder 42: 16)
- Clips, Panama, Oct.-Dec. 1990 (Box-folder 42: 17)
- Clips, Panama, Jan.-May 1991 (Box-folder 42: 18)
- Panama, map (Box-folder 42: 19)
- Miscellany (Box-folder 42: 20)
- Text (Box-folder 42: 21)
- House repair (Box-folder 42: 22)
- Appointment book, 1989 (Box-folder 42: 23)
- Elliott Negin, "Fighting the 'Publish and Perish' Syndrome" (Box-folder 43: 1)
- Authors Guild Bulletin issues (Box-folder 43: 2)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 43: 3)
- Authors Guild Bulletin issues (Box-folder 44: 1)
- Panama, FOIA (Box-folder 44: 2)
- Notes, NPR piece (Box-folder 44: 3)
- Notes, Oct.-Nov. 1986 (Box-folder 44: 4)
- N, Wyrough (Box-folder 44: 5)
- Carlos Rodriguez (Box-folder 44: 6)
- N, Maisto/Savage (Box-folder 44: 7)
- N, Mahlstedt (Box-folder 44: 8)
- N, Hewitt (Box-folder 44: 9)
- Kalish, Buffone (Box-folder 44: 10)
- Eisenman, G. Sanchez (Box-folder 44: 11)
- Deborah Demoss (Box-folder 44: 12)
- DEA, Duncan (Box-folder 44: 13)
- Notes, Blum (Box-folder 44: 14)
- N, Blandon (Box-folder 44: 15)
- A-C (Box-folder 44: 16)
- Reviews, Our Man (Box-folder 44: 17)
- Notes (Box-folder 44: 18)
- Jay Lehner (Box-folder 44: 19)
- Hersh, Sy (Box-folder 44: 20)
- Hersh article (Box-folder 44: 21)
- FOIA requests (Box-folder 44: 22)
- Oversize charts of trial witnesses (Box-folder 45: 1)